"Basket of kisses! Basket of kisses!"
The Bad Seed is a drama, horror, thriller film directed by Rob Lowe.
A widower suspects that his seemingly perfect
adolescent daughter is a heartless killer.
Emma, played by Mckenna Grace.
David, played by Rob Lowe.
Chloe, played by Sarah Dugdale.
Angela, played by Cara Buono.
Dr. March, played by Patty McCormack.
Mrs. Ellis, played by Marci T. House.
The Bad Seed is a 2018 American made-for-television horror
drama film directed by Rob Lowe for Lifetime.
Lowe is also executive producer and stars in the film,
alongside Mckenna Grace, Sarah Dugdale, Marci T.
House, Lorne Cardinal, Chris Shields, Cara Buono, and a
special appearance by Patty McCormack.
The horror thriller is based on the 1954 novel by William
March, the 1954 play, and the 1956 film.
The Bad Seed originally aired on Lifetime on September 9, 2018.
This is the second remake of the film, the first being a 1985 film.
On September 16, 2018, a "special edition" of the TV movie was released that
features behind the scenes interviews with Lowe, Grace, and McCormack.
A sequel to the film titled The Bad Seed Returns
was released on September 5, 2022.
The film explores themes of remake, murder, murder confession.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.